TRAN PHU HAO

Test Engineer



Summary:

Extremely passionate, motivated, analytical, critical thinking and innovative Software Test Engineer with over Tyear of experience in function and manual testing, and extensive background in the following broad-based competencies such as mobile devices, web applications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Test Engineer (Software and Devices) & Camera Tuning Engineer

Mobile Star Technology

03/2016 - 10/2017

Responsibility:

Devices testing:

03/2017 - 10/2017

Test and tune auto white balance, auto exposure, noise reduction algorithms for 4 projects by Mediatek tools.

Support to organize Techforum of Mediatek.

Functional and Manual mobile tester: 03/2016 - 06/2017

Write new functional test cases for mobile devices by Word and Excel.

Perform testing for 21 projects like: Mobiistar ZumboJ2, Mobiistar PrimeX2017, Mobiistar PrimeX1, Mobiistar LaiZ14G,...

Test and give feedback to improve user interface design for mobile applications.

Reviewer (Part-time jobs) **Viettablet Chanel**

06/2017 - 07/2017

Responsibility:

Experience, evaluate, write content, film and make video for 2 clips about smartphone cameras with 4000 views to provide information to customers when choosing to buy smartphones.

CONTACT

Cell:

01636248829

Date of Birth:

22 February 1996

Email:

tphao2202@gmail.com

Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/in/tranhao96

Address:

District 8, Ho Chi Minh City

SKILL

Personal skills:

- Good adaptability and quick learning in changing environment.
- Excellent written and verbal communication.
- Excellent logical and critical thinking.
- Ability to work under pressure.
- Excellent self-motivation.

Soft skills:

Leadership









Teamwork and collaborative











Analytical thinking and research











Planing and strategic thinking











TRAN PHU HAO

Test Engineer

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Secretary of Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth Union of the Faculty of College of Information Technology

HCM University of Science

09/2015 - 09/2016

Responsibility:

Lead a team of 8 people responsible for organizing activities.

Co-ordinate programs, draw up plans, divide work, write script, worke as technician in 21 activities for up to 500 students.

Vice Chairman of CKUS Student Volunteer Groups

HCM University of Science 09/2014 - 09/2015

Responsibility:

Organize teambuilding activities, propose and manage of finance.

Founder of Communication Commission C.A.M

HCM University of Science 09/2015 - 09/2016

Responsibility:

Brainstorm ideas, censor media publications in a team of 11 people.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Volunteer Student in Green Summer Volunteer Campaign 2016 at Tho Chu island organized by HCM Communist Youth Union.
- Third prize in the university competition of Testing Reasoning Ability 2016.
- Volunteer Student in Exam Season Supporting Campaign 2015 organized by Vietnam National University, HCM City.
- Encouragement prize in the university competition of Finding the Leader 2014.

SKILL

Technical skill:

Manual testing

Function testing

Quality image analysis

HTML, CSS, Javascript

Photography

Photoshop

Premere

INTERESTS

Traveling

Reading

Psychology

Meditation

Photography

EDUCATION

HCM University of Science:

College of Information Technology